

### Personal information



ophelia.m.aguilar@gmail.com

(+46)760-070035

Vasavägen 24 Solna, Stockholm

#### **Skills**

C#

HTML

CSS

**JavaScript** 

Java

Kotlin

React.js

**React Native** 

Swift

UI

UX

Figma

UML

Scrum

# Languages

Swedish - Native

English - Fluent

## Social media







# **Ophelia Aguilar**

# **Programming Student**

# Summary

I'm a 25-year-old programming student looking for a full-time internship in Stockholm, starting from January until the end of April.

I'm currently studying app development at Stockholms Tekniska Institut. After the internship, I'll be graduating as a full-fledged programmer. Before the internship, I'll also have gathered experience working with backend programming.

I'm a hard worker, curious, and open to everything new. I would like to have the opportunity to learn, contribute and take part in what it is like to work as a programmer by working alongside

## **Education**

## App Development

2021 - 2023

## **Stockholms Tekniska Institut**

The studies are mainly focused on mobile app development. I've also studied project management, UX, UI, and how to build prototypes in Figma.

2020 - 2021 Programming

#### Kvinnofolkhögskolan

I studied the fundamentals of programming. I frequently used UML for projects and used Scrum to sufficiently plan a wedding with a group of classmates.

Society & Behavioral Science 2015 - 2016

Birkagårdens Folkhögskola

2013 - 2015 Art & Design

Cybergymnasiet

# Work experience

Warehouse Worker

April 2022 - September 2022

**Mopedrenovering** 

**Programming Intern** 

**April 2021 - May 2021** 

## **Albert Schapiro Autonomo**

I mainly focused on building and improving their website, using React.js

Claims Adjuster **February 2020 - July 2020** 

**AmTrust Insurance Services Sweden** 

Sales Advisor October 2019 – January 2020

H&M

Customer Service Employee & Insurance Agent **August 2018 - April 2019** 

mySafety Försäkringar

**July 2016 - August 2018** Additional work experience

I worked as a Barista and Restaurant Staff at MAX Hamburgare, Espresso House, and Burger King.